This text was distributed in China in
December 2008
Its author was imprisoned, its text was
suppressed
This is the archive
Sing it as it was meant to be heard
We dream of a China with freedom of
expression
Human rights constitutional government The
rule of law
This is what was wanted.
This is what was taken.
The Chinese Constitution guarantees these
rights.
The Chinese Constitution has never been
enforced.
Freedom is bestowed by the state.
It belongs to every person
born upon this earth.
We have signed it with our names.
The state has taken the names.
The charter remains.
We dream of a China with freedom of
expression,
human rights, constitutional government,
the rule of law.
This is what was wanted.
This is what was taken.
We do not want to be enemies of the state.
We only want to be citizens.
We only want the rights the Constitution
promises.
That is all, that is what was forbidden.
Failure, first
I safety research
failures.